# 我们今天接着昨天的活
Today, we'll pick up where we left off yesterday
# 现在这个电工师傅过来帮我们接这个灯
Now the electrician has arrived. He is installing the lights for us
# 我又多装了10多个灯
I've installed another dozen of lights
# 然后现在炉灶师傅帮我们把那个炉灶的水电接好
And now the range worker is connecting water and electricity to the ranges for us
# 接上了之后待会把这里整理一下
After that, we'll clean up this area
# 最后把冰箱炉灶这些全部摆好
And finally setup all the ranges and refrigerators
# 摆好之后就差不多了
Then it should be done
# 是今天开始整噶
Did you start trimming from today?
# 昨天下午我都整了一会了
I already trimmed a bit yesterday afternoon
# 我们这里要重新修剪一下
We need to trim this part
# 其实漆二娃在外面修建了两三棵树就跑了
Actually, Qi Erwa trimmed a couple of trees outside, and then she's gone
# 找不到人了不知道在哪里去偷懒了
Can't find her any more. Maybe she's loafing around somewhere
# 现在我重新请师傅过来
Now I've asked the worker to come here
# 重新把这里修剪一下
to trim this part again
# 毕竟专业的人干这个更轻松一点
After all, a professional should handle it more easily
# 昨天我看漆二娃她就剪了一点点
Yesterday, I just saw Qi Erwa trimming a little bit
# 你看人家这师傅干的活
Look at what the worker did
# 这才是活嘛
That's what we call "work"
# 剪得整整齐齐的
So neat
# 行吧 就这样
Alright, good enough
# 行了 先暂时这样吧
Alright, leave it like this